Because you just spend so much time in
your own head. And like I think that's
been really cool. Like you almost like
redevelop your relationship with
yourself because you spend so much time
with yourself. And you can't like
gaslight your way out of it. It's like
if you quit a run early, like there's no
one to blame but yourself.
>> Yeah, and you know what I mean? I mean
it's not the
it is it's not that you are like putting
things in your backpack and then you own
that. It's like
every time I like every race that you
start, you you start from
from zero. It's not because you have
been winning all that that that you are
already on that position. It's like you
need to confront yourself every time and
and and see that. So that's a that's the
a cool thing about
about the sport and the hard thing about
the sport, too. It's uh